# Anamoul Rouf

I'm a **Product Designer** with more than **7 years** of working experience in building bridges between business, technology and human.

I've helped startups and product-driven companies to build **7+ mobile apps, 10+ web applications**, and 25+ websites. I believe in design practice that is data-informed and driven by empathy. I'm passionate about finding the balance between complex business requirements and user needs, through a user-centered design process.

#### Work History

Product Designer at Curogram From APR 2022 to Continue.

Curogram is a communications tool for medical offices.

- Effectively communicate research findings, conceptual ideas, detailed design, and design rationale both verbally and visually
- Develop diagrams, wireframes, visual mockups, click-through, and prototypes.
- **Develop and maintain** a **Design System** for all platforms and help the team to work more efficiently and consistently.

Product Design Manager at Truck Lagbe Limited From MAY 2021 to MAY 2022.

Truck Lagbe is the largest and pioneer in truck & pickup rental service provider.

- I led the most talented team of 5+ designers and designed **functional and useable products** for the current **2M+ & future billion** users through **mobile**, **web**, **B2B** apps.
- I worked collaboratively with cross-functional teams including Tech, Business, Marketing, and other groups.
- Conceived, planned and drove the development of high-end, useful digital products.
- Designed and evaluated a centralized Design System and maintained consistency and continuity, saveing around 25% of designers' and developers' productive time.

Sr. Product Designer at ShareTrip Inc. From SEP 2018 to APR 2021.

ShareTrip is the country's first and pioneer online travel aggregator (OTA).

- I have designed functional and delightful experience through mobile, web, B2C & B2B apps. for 1.2M+ & future billion users.
- Assembled informative insights from research and interviews. Made strategic
  decisions using rapidly testing and design thinking approach, improved usability by
  about 54%.
- Collaborated & co-ordinated with CEO, engineers, and other stakeholders to define UX problems and improve user engagement and generated about 56% growth in active users in 4 months.
- Created seamless and intuitive booking experience through the platform with about 86% success rate.
- Facilitated the design team in developing and maintaining the design system, implementing the design process to increase team productivity by around 25%.

UX Consultant (part-time) at JoBike From JAN 2019 to From JUN 2019.

Jobike is an on-demand bicycle-sharing service. Worked on 3+ web & mobile apps.

- Redesign & automate the support system and also enhance the bicycle battery efficiency by 30%.
- Designed a more improved & secured user account recharge process, which helps to get positive user reviews.

- +880 175 969 3045
- anamoulrouf.bd@gmail.com
- anamoulrouf.com
- anamoulrouf.com/portfolio
- in linkedin.com/in/roufuxdesigner

## Education

# Google UX

Google Career Certificates (Coursera) 2020 - 21

### **Design Thinking for Innovation**

Darden School of Business (Coursera) 2020 - 21

#### Conducting Usability Testing

IDF 2020 - 21

# **Human-Centered Design**

UCSan Diego (Coursera) 2019 - 20

#### Gamification

University of Pennsylvania (Coursera) 2020 - 21

#### BBS, Business Studies

National University, Bangladesh 2005 - 09

#### + More

#### Skills

User Interview	<ul> <li>Usability Testing</li> </ul>
OSCI II ILCI VICVV	· Obubility resting

User Research

Think Alouds

Rapid Prototyj
 Visual Design

Contextual InquiryPersona

Responsive Design

Scenario

Design System

Storyboarding

Design

Information

Documentation

Architects

Design HandoverIteration

SketchesWireframing

Problem Solving

Heuristic Evaluation

Problem Solving

Troditotio E taraderon

Interaction Design

#### + More

#### Tools

Figma

• Adobe XD

FigJam

Adobe Creative Suit

BalsamiqMiro

ZeplinNotion

+ More

# Work Interest

- Augmented Reality (AR) Virtual Reality (VR)
- Design for Al-Driven Tech
- Problem Solving by Product Design
- User Survey Data Analysis.